<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Reference on Satellite</title>
    <link>https://lkummer.github.io/Satellite/v1.0.0/reference/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Reference on Satellite</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://lkummer.github.io/Satellite/v1.0.0/reference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Color Customization</title>
      <link>https://lkummer.github.io/Satellite/v1.0.0/reference/customization/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lkummer.github.io/Satellite/v1.0.0/reference/customization/</guid>
      <description>Looking to make your Satellite website yours? You arrived at the right place. This page lists all color customization options Satellite offers.
Each section of a Satellite site can be colored independently, allowing you to theme your website however you want.
Colors can be customized using params.colors configuration options. This page lists all color options. Check out the config example at the bottom for a concrete example.
Primary Colors Used for the main section of the website, where content is displayed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Icons and Logos</title>
      <link>https://lkummer.github.io/Satellite/v1.0.0/reference/icons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lkummer.github.io/Satellite/v1.0.0/reference/icons/</guid>
      <description>Want to make your Satellite website pop with beautiful SVG logos? This page contains everything you need to know to configure the customizable icons and logos of your Satellite website.
Favicon The favicon can be customized using the params.icons.favicon configuration option. However, you also need to host your favicon.
Place the favicon in the static/ folder of the website. It is recommended to use a subfolder, such as static/images/. With your icon in the static folder, set params.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menus and Navigation</title>
      <link>https://lkummer.github.io/Satellite/v1.0.0/reference/menus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lkummer.github.io/Satellite/v1.0.0/reference/menus/</guid>
      <description>This document assumes basic knowledge of Hugo menus.
Top Navigation The params.logoPermalink option can be used to set where the top navigation logo links to. By default the logo links to the site&amp;rsquo;s index.
The main menu entries are listed in the top navigation bar and in the mobile hamburger menu. Note that weight can be set to order menu items.
Pages on the website can be added to the main menu through front matter options, for example:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search Engine Optimizations</title>
      <link>https://lkummer.github.io/Satellite/v1.0.0/reference/seo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lkummer.github.io/Satellite/v1.0.0/reference/seo/</guid>
      <description>Do you need Google enhanced search results and enhanced social media sharing? This page documents Satellite&amp;rsquo;s SEO related configuration options.
General The title and params.seo.description configuration options can be used to set a title and description for your website.
title = &amp;#34;Satellite&amp;#34; [params] [params.seo] description = &amp;#34;Satellite Hugo theme demo.&amp;#34; In content pages, the title and description of the current page are used.
Twitter and Facebook Twitter and facebook allow specifying an image for your website.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
